Finding Aid for Hospitals (University of Michigan) records, 1875-2005
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Nursing
  - Associate Director for Nursing
    - McMahon, Sue
      - Projects and Programs
        - Establishing a Computerized Medical Information System 1980 (Box 149)
        - Establishing an Automated Information System 1980 (Box 149)
        - Food Service Design Program 1981 (Box 149)
        - Friesen No-Nursing Station Concept 1970 (Box 149)
        - Functional and Space Program 1981, 2 folders (Box 149)
        - Guest Relations Program (Box 149)
        - Information Systems Strategic Plan 1983 (Box 149)
        - Inpatient Modernization Program 1971 (Box 149)
        - >Long Range Plan Draft 1972 (Box 150)
        - Management by Objectives Workshop 1972 (Box 150)
        - Nurse Instructor Training Program -- Instructor Manual 1985 (Box 150)
        - Nursing Services 5-Year Plan 1981 (Box 150)
        - Productivity and Quality Program 1984 (Box 150)
        - Project Management Guide 1978 (Box 150)
        - Replacement and Renovation of Components at the Hospital 1979 (Box 150)
        - Replacement Hospital Project 1985 (Box 150)
        - Revision of Space Program Narrative 1981, 3 folders (Box 150)
        - Youth Mentoring Program 1994, 2 folders (Box 150)
      - Reports
        - Activation Conference Report 1983 (Box 150)
        - Burns Report (Box 150)
        - Executive Board Report on Inpatient Units 1983 (Box 150)
        - Inpatient Care Unites S&E Revised Report 1980 (Box 150)
        - Inpatient Census System Requirements Definition Report 1982 (Box 150)
        - Nursing Labor Distribution Report 1983 (Box 150)
        - Staffing Charts and Reports 1983 (Box 150)
        - Status Report 1980 (Box 150)
        - Case Mix and Length of Stay Study 1976 (Box 151)
        - Employee Attitude Survey 1980 (Box 151)
        - Faculty Research 1979, 1982 (Box 151)
        - Graduate Student Research Abstracts 1981 (Box 151)
        - Kellogg Eye Center Nursing Staff Survey 1990 (Box 151)
        - Nurse Retention Survey 1971, 1978 (Box 151)
        - Nursing Services Questionnaire 1976-1978 (Box 151)
        - Patient Satisfaction Comparison 1987 (Box 151)
        - Patient Survey Results 1989 (Box 151)
        - Position Questionnaire (Box 151)
        - Results of the Advertising and Opinion Survey 1987 (Box 151)
        - Smoking Survey Summary 1981 (Box 151)
      - Topical
        - "A Nursing Perspective of the Eradication of Smallpox" 1980 (Box 151)
        - "A Sensor and Monitor for the Manpower Control System" 1973 (Box 151)
        - Administration Time-Related Drug Interactions 1990 (Box 151)
        - Administrative Library 1982 (Box 151)
        - Advances in Rehabilitation Nursing Conference 2001, 2002, 2 folders (Box 151)
        - Communication Issues (Box 151)
        - Correspondence 1986, 1995-1996 (Box 151)
        - Diagnosis Related Groups 1981-1983 (Box 151)
        - Executive Briefing 1979 (Box 151)
        - Faculty Meeting 1997 (Box 151)
        - Glossary of Terminology (Box 151)
        - Hospital Publications 1985 (Box 151)
        - Hospital Role and Mission Statement 1977 (Box 151)
        - "Impact of Computerized Hospital Information Systems" 1975 (Box 151)
        - Manual Order Entry and Results Reporting Systems Phase I 1981 (Box 151)
        - Manual Order Entry and Results Reporting Systems Phase II 1982
          - Manual Order Entry and Results Reports and Proposals 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box 152)
        - Manual Order Entry and Results Task Force 1981-1982, 2 folders (Box 152)
        - Material Management and Handling Services 1980 (Box 152)
        - Material Service Center Changes 1991 (Box 152)
        - Medical Center Activity (Box 152)
        - Memoirs (about the hospital) 1981-1982 (Box 152)
        - Michigan Organization for Human Rights 1989-1991 (Box 152)
        - National Leadership Conference 1993 (Box 152)
        - National Leadership Conference Abstracts 1993 (Box 152)
        - National Leadership Conference Abstracts 1995 (Box 152)
        - Nursing Article Notecards 1960 (Box 152)
        - Nursing Newsletters 1982-1991 (Box 152)
        - Organizational Chart 1979 (Box 152)
        - Pre-op Notes Newsletter 1973-1974 (Box 152)
        - Problem Oriented Recording Manual 1989 (Box 152)
        - Senior Team Leader Notes 1965-1968, 1976 (Box 152)
        - Sigma Theta Tau 1982-1984, 1987 (Box 152)
        - Systems and Elements Studies Work Group -- Material Management 1980 (Box 152)
        - The Integrator Newsletter 1994-1995 (Box 152)
        - Work Redesign: Challenges and Opportunities (Box 152)
    - Sample, Sally (Box 138)
      - Committees
        - Ad Hoc Committee to Establish Feasibility of Monitor Technician Program (Box 138)
        - Classification Study Steering Committee 1982-1984 (Box 138)
        - Clinical Practice Guidelines Committee 1976 (Box 138)
        - Clinician Program Evaluation Committee Report 1977 (Box 138)
        - Collaborative Practice Committee
          - Articles 1984 (Box 138)
          - Beyond Rhetoric to Reality 1982-1983 (Box 138)
          - Conference 1981-1985, 2 folders (Box 138)
          - Correspondence 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box 138)
          - Credentialing 1988-1989 (Box 138)
          - Credentialing Requests 1988 (Box 138)
          - Designs for the Future 1985 (Box 138)
          - Minutes 1985, 1986, 4 folders (Box 138)
        - Coordinating Committee Objectives 1987-1988 (Box 138)
        - Faculty Service Committee 1980-1981 (Box 138)
        - Joint Practice Committee
          - General 1984-1985 (Box 138)
          - Establishment Proposal 1978 (Box 138)
          - Meeting Minutes 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box 139)
          - Meeting Minutes 1983 (Box 139)
          - Meeting Minutes 1984, 2 folders (Box 139)
        - Medical Center Alumni Visiting Committee 1981 (Box 139)
        - Nurse Retention Committee Report 1980 (Box 139)
        - Nursing Committees 1985 (Box 139)
        - Nursing Information Systems Coordinating Committee Meeting Minutes 1987-1989 (Box 139)
        - Nursing Network Committee Summary Report 1981 (Box 139)
        - Nursing Practice Committee 1982-1984, 1988 (Box 139)
        - Research Review and Study Committee 1979 (Box 139)
        - Retention Committee 1978 (Box 139)
        - Standing Committees 1982 (Box 139)
      - Events
        - Administrative Nursing Forum 1982-1983 (Box 139)
        - Administrative Nursing Retreat 1982 (Box 139)
        - Collaborative Practice 3rd Annual Conference 1985 (Box 139)
        - Fourth Annual Primary Nursing Symposium 1988 (Box 139)
        - Leadership Conference Abstracts 1986 (Box 139)
        - National Nursing Conference 1990, 1991, 2 folders (Box 139)
        - National Nursing Conference on Leadership 1988 (Box 139)
        - Nursing Forum Agenda 1988 (Box 139)
        - School of Nursing Retreat May 7-8, 1985 (Box 139)
      - Nurse Employment
        - Assistant Head Nurse Classification 1984-1987 (Box 139)
        - Clinical Ladder 1985 (Box 139)
        - Clinical Nurse I and II 1982-1986 (Box 139)
        - Clinical Nurse Specialist (Box 139)
        - Contracting with Outside Agencies for Nursing Personnel 1977 (Box 140)
        - Dress and Appearance Standard 1986 (Box 140)
        - Educational Coordinator Position (Box 140)
        - Employee Loan 1979 (Box 140)
        - Faculty Collaboration 1985-1988 (Box 140)
        - Guidelines for Excessive Absenteeism 1981 (Box 140)
        - Guidelines for Nursing Administrative Externship 1977 (Box 140)
        - Head Nurse Description 1980 (Box 140)
        - Hemodialysis LPN Classification 1984 (Box 140)
        - Hospital Executive Board Status Report on Staff 1980 (Box 140)
        - LPN Description Feedback (Box 140)
        - MNA Strike 1981, 1987 (Box 140)
        - Nurse Aide Classification 1982 (Box 140)
        - Nurse Recruitment Plan Analysis 1981 (Box 140)
        - Nurse Staffing Reports 1983 (Box 140)
        - Nurse Turnover 1982-1984 (Box 140)
        - Nurses Strike 1989 (Box 140)
        - Nursing Classification Study Results 1982-1984 (Box 140)
        - Nursing Staff Matrix 1980, 1984 (Box 140)
        - Performance Evaluation and Goals 1983 (Box 140)
        - Performance Plan for Lillian Simms 1981-1982 (Box 140)
        - Position Classification Descriptions 1984 (Box 140)
        - Post-Strike Transition 1981-1982 (Box 140)
        - Proposal -- Nurse Staffing Study 1978 (Box 140)
        - Resolution of Nurse Staffing Problems (Box 140)
        - Salary Program Enhancements 1987 (Box 140)
        - Salary-Setting Procedures 1985 (Box 140)
        - Staff Interview Summaries 1980 (Box 140)
        - Status Report on Nurse Staffing 1987 (Box 140)
        - A Survey of Hospital Nurses 1981, 2 folders (Box 140)
      - Nursing Director's Council
        - Activation Operational Workplans 1984 (Box 140)
        - Activation Training and Orientation Presentation 1985 (Box 140)
        - Administrative Report 1984 (Box 140)
        - Ambulatory Care Nursing 1985-1986 (Box 140)
        - Change of Pace Discussion 1986 (Box 141)
        - Clinical Policy Procedures 1979-1983, 4 folders (Box 141)
        - Correspondence 1984-1987 (Box 141)
        - Draft Sample Performance Plans 1982 (Box 141)
        - Focus Conference Evaluation 1982 (Box 141)
        - Focus on Nursing Videotape 1982 (Box 141)
        - Focus Retreat 1982, 1983, 1986, 3 folders (Box 141)
        - General 1981 (Box 141)
        - Licensed Practical Nurse Position 1982-1984, 1987 (Box 141)
        - Management Track Task Force 1984 (Box 141)
        - Meeting Minutes June 29, 1982 (Box 141)
        - Meeting Minutes November 30, 1982 (Box 141)
        - Meeting Minutes November 1, 1983 (Box 141)
        - Meeting Minutes May 29, 1984 (Box 141)
        - Meeting Minutes 1987 (Box 141)
        - Meeting Minutes August 29, 1988 (Box 141)
        - Mock Arrest 1985 (Box 141)
        - Mott/Women's/Holden Hospital Services Organization 1982 (Box 141)
        - Nurse Researcher Role 1982 (Box 141)
        - Nursing Classifications 1982-1984 (Box 141)
        - Nursing Management Track Task Force 1984 (Box 141)
        - Nursing Representation Alternative Models 1986 (Box 141)
        - Organizational Charts 1988 (Box 141)
        - Performance Plans 1983 (Box 141)
        - Procedures for Endorsement 1982-1984 (Box 141)
        - Proposal for Charge Nurse Guidelines 1981 (Box 141)
        - Public Hearing 1985 (Box 141)
        - Purpose 1982 (Box 141)
        - Recruitment and Retention Initiatives 1988 (Box 141)
        - Research Program Goals 1983 (Box 141)
        - Retreat August 2-3, 1984 (Box 141)
        - Retreat June 24-26, 1987 (Box 141)
        - Retreat 1988 (Box 141)
        - Salary Placement Task Force 1984 (Box 141)
        - Status Report 1987-1988 (Box 141)
        - Strategic Plan 1988-1991, 1989 (Box 141)
        - Strategic Plan Draft 1987 (Box 141)
        - Strategic Planning Session 1986 (Box 141)
        - Timekeeping System 1983 (Box 141)
      - Patient Care (Box 142)
        - Integrated Inpatient Management Model 1988-1989 (Box 142)
        - Patient Activity Study 1988 (Box 142)
        - Patient Classification System 1977 (Box 142)
        - Patient Classification System Progress Report (Box 142)
        - Presentation to Develop and Implement a System for Assessing and Meeting Patient Care Needs 1979 (Box 142)
        - Proposal for Systems for Assessing and Meeting Patient Care Needs 1978 (Box 142)
        - Proposal Systems for Assessing and Meeting Patient Care Needs 1978 (Box 142)
        - Proposal to Assist in Development of a System for Measuring and Meeting Patient Care Needs 1978 (Box 142)
        - Proposal to Develop and Implement a System for Assessing and Meeting Patient Care Needs -- Supplement 1979 (Box 142)
        - Revised Proposal to Develop and Implement a System for Assessing and Meeting Patient Care Needs 1978 (Box 142)
        - Standards of Care 1989 (Box 142)
        - Systems for Assessing and Meeting Patient Care Needs 1978 (Box 142)
        - TPN Standardized Nursing Care Plans 1979 (Box 142)
      - Programs and Projects
        - Clinical Career Program 1987 (Box 142)
        - Clinical Nursing Career Program 1985-1986 (Box 142)
        - Corporate Nursing Services Programs 1986 (Box 142)
        - Educational Services Programs 1980-1981 (Box 142)
        - Independent Nurse Clinic 1986 (Box 142)
        - Medicus Revalidation Project 1986-1989 (Box 142)
        - Nurse Exam Program 1982-1984 (Box 142)
        - Nurse Recruitment Program Review 1978 (Box 142)
        - Nurse Retention Program 1979, 2 folders (Box 142)
        - Pediatric, Perinatal, and Psychiatric Plans and Structure 1987-1988 (Box 142)
        - Project Research 1985-1987 (Box 142)
        - Quality Assurance Plans 1988 (Box 142)
        - Research Projects 1985 (Box 142)
      - Proposals
        - Development of Nurse Staffing Standards Amended Proposal 1979 (Box 142)
        - Educational Services for Nursing Preceptor Proposal 1982 (Box 142)
        - LPN Scholarship Proposal 1980 (Box 142)
        - Nursing Management Series 1987 (Box 142)
        - Nursing Scholarship Program Proposal 1982 (Box 142)
        - Nursing Target Hours of Care Proposal (Box 142)
        - Proposal for Consulting Services 1978 (Box 142)
        - Psychiatric Nursing Consultation Program Proposal (Box 142)
        - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation Proposal 1989 (Box 143)
      - Publications
        - Assorted Nursing Newsletters 1982-1987 (Box 143)
        - Decision Support System 1988 (Box 143)
        - The Friesen No-Nursing Station Concept 1970 (Box 143)
        - General Publications (Box 143)
        - Home Parental and Enetral Nutrition Manual 1983 (Box 143)
        - Management Modules for Nursing Services Module 2 1984 (Box 143)
        - Management Modules for Nursing Services Module 3 1982 (Box 143)
        - Nursing Fact Book 1985 (Box 143)
        - Physician Extenders Annotated Bibliography 1976, 2 folders (Box 143)
        - Problem Oriented Record Manual 1976 (Box 143)
        - Published Articles 1988 (Box 143)
      - Reviews and Reports
        - Activity Report 1987 (Box 143)
        - Clinical Needs Final Report 1984 (Box 143)
        - Competencies of Graduates of Nursing Programs 1983 (Box 143)
        - Joint Review of Nursing Services 1980 (May-October) (Box 143)
        - Joint Review of Nursing Services November 1980, 2 folders (Box 143)
        - Medicus Reports with Explanatory notes 1988 (Box 143)
        - Nursing Management Information System Final Report 1983 (Box 143)
        - Nursing Quality Assurance Reports 1989 (Box 143)
        - Nursing Services Organizational Joint Review 1980, 2 folders (Box 143)
        - Nursing Services Organizational Review 1979-1980 (Box 143)
        - Primary Nursing Final Report 1981 (Box 144)
        - Recruitment and Retention Status Report 1988 (Box 144)
        - Secretary's Commission Final Report Vol. 1 1988 (Box 144)
        - Secretary's Commission on Nursing Summary 1988 (Box 144)
      - Task Forces
        - Career Ladder Task Force Report 1983 (Box 144)
        - Clinical/Career Ladder Task Force 1983 (Box 144)
        - Computer Education Record Keeping Task Force 1989 (Box 144)
        - Dress Code Task Force Report 1981 (Box 144)
        - JCAHO Task Force 1991 (Box 144)
        - Licensed Practical Nurse Role Definition Task Force (Box 144)
        - Licensed Practical Nurse Task Force 1981 (Box 144)
        - Licensed Practical Nurse Task Force 1985, 2 folders (Box 144)
        - Management Development for Nurses Task Force 1989 (Box 144)
        - Management Track Task Force 1982-1984 (Box 144)
        - Management Track Task Force Report 1984 (Box 144)
        - Nursing Management Task Force 1981 (Box 144)
        - Role and Utilization of Clinical Nurse Specialist Task Force Report 1983 (Box 144)
      - Topical Files
        - Action Plan for Minimum Nursing Data Set 1989 (Box 144)
        - Ad Hoc Nursing Development Council 1979 (Box 144)
        - ANSOS Station 1987-1988 (Box 144)
        - Clinical Initiatives 1985 (Box 144)
        - Correspondence
          - 1981, 1984 (Box 144)
          - 1986 (Box 144)
          - 1987, 4 folders (Box 144)
          - 1988, 3 folders (Box 145)
          - 1989, 2 folders (Box 145)
        - Course Evaluation Prospect Payment and DRG's 1983 (Box 145)
        - Data from Head Nurse 1977 (Box 145)
        - Exit Questionnaire Data 1981-1982 (Box 145)
        - Expense Reduction 1984-1987 (Box 145)
        - Future Nursing Initiatives 1989 (Box 145)
        - General Administration 1982-1988 (Box 145)
        - Graduate Program Recommendations 1988 (Box 145)
        - Informed Consent Survey 1990 (Box 145)
        - Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals 1979-1981 (Box 145)
        - Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals 1984 (Box 145)
        - Masters of Science in Nursing Administration (Box 145)
        - Medication Administration Policy 1985 (Box 145)
        - Medicus Type 5 Methodology 1983 (Box 145)
        - New York Medical Center Criteria (Box 145)
        - Nursing Executive Council Meeting Minutes 1991 (Box 145)
        - Nursing Information Systems Planning Effort 1982 (Box 145)
        - Nursing Practice Changes 1984 (Box 145)
        - Perspective in Nursing Services 1985 (Box 145)
        - Preservation of Nursing Service Documents 1985 (Box 145)
        - Visiting Nurse Association 1986 (Box 145)
    - Vose, Jackson, and Sample (Box 74)
      - Board of Clinical Directors
        - Minutes 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 74)
          (continues as the Nursing Executive Committee)
      - Nursing Executive Committee
        - Minutes 1978-1980, 5 folders (Box 74)
        - Committees Files (Box 74)
      - Nursing Administrative Staff and Council of Nursing Services (Box 75)
        - Minutes 1976-1977 (Box 75)
      - Council of Nursing Services
        - Minutes 1978-1979 (Box 75)
      - Topical Files
        - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees 1970-1979 (Box 75)
        - Annual Reports Materials (Box 75)
        - Areas of Responsibility, Nursing Administrators (Box 75)
        - Associate Director for Nursing Staff Meetings 1981 (Box 75)
        - Budget Files 1970-1977, 5 folders (Box 75)
        - Burn Center, Program Proposal for Expanded 1978 (Box 75)
        - Chief of Nursing (Box 75)
        - Correspondence 1975-1979 (Box 75)
        - Objectives and Position Description (Box 75)
        - Clinical Directors 1976-1978 (Box 75)
        - Clinical Nursing Specialist 1970-1978 (Box 75)
        - Clinician Position 1974-1979 (Box 75)
        - Commodity Acquisition and Utilization (Box 76)
        - Criterion measures of nursing care 1976 (Box 76)
        - Dalston, Jeptha 1976 (Box 76)
        - Decentralization 1970-1971 (Box 76)
        - Discharge Planning and Management 1977 and 1984-1985 (Box 76)
        - Employee Health Service Task Force 1977 (Box 76)
        - Family Practice Accreditation Proposal 1978 (Box 76)
        - In-Patient Nursing Care Activity Profile 1973 (Box 76)
        - Joint Commission on the Accreditation of Hospitals 1975-1979 (Box 76)
        - Joint Conference Committee on Nursing 1976-1979 (Box 76)
        - Joint Review of Nursing Services 1980 (Box 76)
        - Licensed Practical Nurses 1970-1976 (Box 76)
        - Management by Objectives 1973-1974 (Box 76)
        - Medical Center Review Committee 1973 (Box 76)
        - Medical Service Plan 1976 (Box 76)
        - Michigan Department of Public Health Facility Evaluation Report and Responses 1979 (Box 76)
        - Michigan Nurses Association 1973-1978 (Box 76)
        - Nursing Administration Office Staffing Study 1979 (Box 77)
        - Nursing Administrative Staff Meetings and Workshops 1973-1977 (Box 77)
        - Nursing Budget Task Force 1974 (Box 77)
        - Nursing Computer Planning Committee 1972-1979 (Box 77)
        - Nursing Directors Council Minutes 1981 (Box 77)
        - Nursing Network Committee 1981-1982 (Box 77)
        - Nursing Planning Committee 1982 (Box 77)
        - Nursing Practice Committee 1977-1979 (Box 77)
        - Nursing Role Matrix Committee 1980 (Box 77)
        - Nursing Shortage 1969 (Box 77)
        - Operating Room 1975-1977 (Box 77)
        - Operations Review Proposals and related 1985, 2 folders (Box 77)
        - Ophthalmology: Program Proposal for Consolidation of Ophthalmology Services at the Parkview/Turner Hospital 1978 (Box 77)
        - Organization (Box 78)
          (University Hospital, etc.)
        - Organization and operation of the Office of the Chief of Nursing (Box 78)
        - Outpatient Clinic 1973-1977 (Box 78)
        - Outside Agencies 1977 (Box 78)
          (contracting with outside agencies for nursing personnel)
        - Patient Care--Systems for Assessing and Meeting Patient Care Needs: Working Paper 1, Requirements Study 1978 (Box 78)
        - Pediatric Nurse Practitioner Associates, Guidelines for Non-Hospital Based 1978 (Box 78)
        - Philosophy/Nursing Service Mission 1977 and 1979 (Box 78)
        - Professional Achievements 1884/85 and 1986/87 (Box 78)
        - Role Transformation Study 1974-1976 (Box 78)
        - St. Joseph Mercy Hospital (old hospital) Renovation Proposals 1979 (Box 78)
        - Staffing Guidelines 1974 (Box 78)
        - University Hospital: Replacement & Renovation of Selective Components 1979 (Box 78)
  - Clinical Nursing Specialist Program
    - Development of Program 1971-1980 (Box 38)
    - Mental Health Nursing in Obstetrics 1976-1978 (Box 38)
    - Nursing Shortage Information 1969-1970 (Box 38)
    - Symposium Papers Presented 1972 (Box 38)
  - Educational Services for Nursing
    - Administrative Orientation Manual 1984 (Box 153)
    - Adult Medical-Surgical Nurse Internship Program Proposal 1990 (Box 153)
    - Advance Teaching Strategies (Box 153)
    - Agendas and Minutes 1990, 1 binder (Box 157)
    - Alumni (Box 153)
      - Medical Center 1990-1992 (Box 153)
      - New Graduates (Box 153)
      - Medical Center Alumni Board of Governors Meeting 1992 (Box 153)
    - Computer Assisted Learning 1990 (Box 153)
    - Contract Agency Orientation (Box 153)
    - Clinical Laboratory Tests (Box 153)
    - Continuing Education Task Force 1983 (Box 153)
    - Decentralized/Centralized Educational Services 1980-1982 (Box 153)
    - Director's Information 1981 (Box 153)
    - Educational Services for Nursing Manual (Box 153)
    - Educational Videos, 2 video tapes (Box 157)
    - Educational Work Group 1980-1982 (Box 154)
    - Entry into Nursing Practice (Box 154)
    - Hospitals
      - Budget (Box 154)
      - Nurse's Survey 1981 (Box 154)
      - Organization 1986-1991 (Box 154)
      - Records 1979 (Box 154)
    - JCAHO Manual 1992 (Box 154)
    - Management Committee and Group Forum Policy Document 1981 (Box 154)
    - Medical Center HC 1990 (Box 154)
    - Mott Annex 1978-1983 (Box 154)
    - MWH Team 1988 (Box 154)
    - News Clippings 1989-1990 (Box 154)
    - Newsletters 1975-1999, 5 folders (Box 154)
    - Newsletters 1975-1999 (Box 155)
    - Nurse Instructor Training Program (Box 155)
    - Nursing
      - Assignment Patterns User's Manual 1978 (Box 155)
      - Directors Council 1989 (Box 155)
      - Education Conference 1980 (Box 155)
      - Information Systems Committee 1990 (Box 155)
      - Orientation 1989, 2 folders (Box 155)
      - Education Overview, volumes 1-2 and 4-5, 4 binders (Box 158)
      - Services 1980-1982 (Box 155)
    - Operating Room Programs 1976 (Box 155)
    - Order Entry Results Report 1984 (Box 155)
    - Pamphlets 1986-1990 (Box 155)
    - Peritoneal Dialysis Training Program Manual, 1 binder (Box 157)